{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731052151","data":{"timestamp":" 947731052151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGOE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731053868","data":{"timestamp":" 947731053867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731065526","data":{"timestamp":" 947731065526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731066756","data":{"timestamp":" 947731066756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731068593","data":{"timestamp":" 947731068593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731070833","data":{"timestamp":" 947731070833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731072865","data":{"timestamp":" 947731072865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731074009","data":{"timestamp":" 947731074009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEENDA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731076221","data":{"timestamp":" 947731076221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731078539","data":{"timestamp":" 947731078539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731080474","data":{"timestamp":" 947731080474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731082944","data":{"timestamp":" 947731082944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731084610","data":{"timestamp":" 947731084610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731086781","data":{"timestamp":" 947731086781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731088744","data":{"timestamp":" 947731088744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731091602","data":{"timestamp":" 947731091602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731093327","data":{"timestamp":" 947731093326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731093852","data":{"timestamp":" 947731093851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731095774","data":{"timestamp":" 947731095774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731105037","data":{"timestamp":" 947731105036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731107389","data":{"timestamp":" 947731107389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731109662","data":{"timestamp":" 947731109662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731111778","data":{"timestamp":" 947731111778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731113882","data":{"timestamp":" 947731113882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731115677","data":{"timestamp":" 947731115677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731117431","data":{"timestamp":" 947731117431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731119362","data":{"timestamp":" 947731119362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731121367","data":{"timestamp":" 947731121367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731123023","data":{"timestamp":" 947731123023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731126413","data":{"timestamp":" 947731126412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731128110","data":{"timestamp":" 947731128110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731128195","data":{"timestamp":" 947731128195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731140625","data":{"timestamp":" 947731140624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 48676a2b-5941-46fe-ad2b-736055699879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731159054","data":{"timestamp":" 947731159054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" caa0f848-5e4f-4a64-89ef-f3eb4f242f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731161704","data":{"timestamp":" 947731161704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" caa0f848-5e4f-4a64-89ef-f3eb4f242f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731163111","data":{"timestamp":" 947731163111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" caa0f848-5e4f-4a64-89ef-f3eb4f242f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731164560","data":{"timestamp":" 947731164560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" caa0f848-5e4f-4a64-89ef-f3eb4f242f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731164683","data":{"timestamp":" 947731164682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" caa0f848-5e4f-4a64-89ef-f3eb4f242f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731170668","data":{"timestamp":" 947731170668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" caa0f848-5e4f-4a64-89ef-f3eb4f242f89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731185359","data":{"timestamp":" 947731185359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731187612","data":{"timestamp":" 947731187611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731189765","data":{"timestamp":" 947731189765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731191654","data":{"timestamp":" 947731191654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731195233","data":{"timestamp":" 947731195233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731199040","data":{"timestamp":" 947731199040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731201184","data":{"timestamp":" 947731201183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731203372","data":{"timestamp":" 947731203372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731209600","data":{"timestamp":" 947731209600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731212291","data":{"timestamp":" 947731212291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731214727","data":{"timestamp":" 947731214727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731217400","data":{"timestamp":" 947731217400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731219356","data":{"timestamp":" 947731219355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731222016","data":{"timestamp":" 947731222016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731225357","data":{"timestamp":" 947731225357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731226096","data":{"timestamp":" 947731226096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731226494","data":{"timestamp":" 947731226494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731228768","data":{"timestamp":" 947731228768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731231011","data":{"timestamp":" 947731231011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731232832","data":{"timestamp":" 947731232831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731236852","data":{"timestamp":" 947731236851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731239521","data":{"timestamp":" 947731239521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731241571","data":{"timestamp":" 947731241571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731243571","data":{"timestamp":" 947731243571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731246043","data":{"timestamp":" 947731246042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BONDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731247513","data":{"timestamp":" 947731247513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731250031","data":{"timestamp":" 947731250031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINGILO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731252203","data":{"timestamp":" 947731252203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731255412","data":{"timestamp":" 947731255412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731259380","data":{"timestamp":" 947731259380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731262108","data":{"timestamp":" 947731262108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731265280","data":{"timestamp":" 947731265280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731269386","data":{"timestamp":" 947731269386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731272144","data":{"timestamp":" 947731272144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731274058","data":{"timestamp":" 947731274058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731276586","data":{"timestamp":" 947731276586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731280393","data":{"timestamp":" 947731280393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731282710","data":{"timestamp":" 947731282709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731284851","data":{"timestamp":" 947731284851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731287025","data":{"timestamp":" 947731287025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731292648","data":{"timestamp":" 947731292648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731295094","data":{"timestamp":" 947731295094"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731298377","data":{"timestamp":" 947731298377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731301955","data":{"timestamp":" 947731301955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731304322","data":{"timestamp":" 947731304322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731306139","data":{"timestamp":" 947731306139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731309134","data":{"timestamp":" 947731309134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731311621","data":{"timestamp":" 947731311621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731313987","data":{"timestamp":" 947731313987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731315838","data":{"timestamp":" 947731315838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731317696","data":{"timestamp":" 947731317696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731319286","data":{"timestamp":" 947731319286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731320903","data":{"timestamp":" 947731320903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731322735","data":{"timestamp":" 947731322735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731324319","data":{"timestamp":" 947731324319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731325491","data":{"timestamp":" 947731325490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOCHEZA"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731327204","data":{"timestamp":" 947731327204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOCHEZA"," userResponse":" MABAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731329149","data":{"timestamp":" 947731329148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOCHEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731330306","data":{"timestamp":" 947731330306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731331626","data":{"timestamp":" 947731331626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731332646","data":{"timestamp":" 947731332646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIZA"," userResponse":" MABAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731337049","data":{"timestamp":" 947731337049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731338880","data":{"timestamp":" 947731338880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731341015","data":{"timestamp":" 947731341015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731342847","data":{"timestamp":" 947731342847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731345018","data":{"timestamp":" 947731345018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731345838","data":{"timestamp":" 947731345837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731348681","data":{"timestamp":" 947731348681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIMKASIRISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731351978","data":{"timestamp":" 947731351978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731353883","data":{"timestamp":" 947731353883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731355230","data":{"timestamp":" 947731355229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731356263","data":{"timestamp":" 947731356263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731357662","data":{"timestamp":" 947731357662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731358611","data":{"timestamp":" 947731358610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731361100","data":{"timestamp":" 947731361099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731363124","data":{"timestamp":" 947731363123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731367984","data":{"timestamp":" 947731367984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731369822","data":{"timestamp":" 947731369822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731376371","data":{"timestamp":" 947731376371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINACHOKUWEZESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731378317","data":{"timestamp":" 947731378317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731380512","data":{"timestamp":" 947731380512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGIZAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731382228","data":{"timestamp":" 947731382228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731385513","data":{"timestamp":" 947731385513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAARUFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731387875","data":{"timestamp":" 947731387875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731389932","data":{"timestamp":" 947731389932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731391600","data":{"timestamp":" 947731391600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731393395","data":{"timestamp":" 947731393395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731395078","data":{"timestamp":" 947731395078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731396956","data":{"timestamp":" 947731396956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731398880","data":{"timestamp":" 947731398880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINENE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731404864","data":{"timestamp":" 947731404864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731407244","data":{"timestamp":" 947731407244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731409514","data":{"timestamp":" 947731409514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731412051","data":{"timestamp":" 947731412051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDEKEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731413834","data":{"timestamp":" 947731413834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731415768","data":{"timestamp":" 947731415767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731418049","data":{"timestamp":" 947731418049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHINDANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731419837","data":{"timestamp":" 947731419837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731421884","data":{"timestamp":" 947731421883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731424338","data":{"timestamp":" 947731424338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731426831","data":{"timestamp":" 947731426831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731428632","data":{"timestamp":" 947731428632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731430985","data":{"timestamp":" 947731430985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731432870","data":{"timestamp":" 947731432870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731435733","data":{"timestamp":" 947731435733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731437823","data":{"timestamp":" 947731437823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731440114","data":{"timestamp":" 947731440114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731442100","data":{"timestamp":" 947731442100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731444712","data":{"timestamp":" 947731444712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731449826","data":{"timestamp":" 947731449826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731451291","data":{"timestamp":" 947731451291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731453757","data":{"timestamp":" 947731453757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731455998","data":{"timestamp":" 947731455998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731465098","data":{"timestamp":" 947731465097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHINDWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731466785","data":{"timestamp":" 947731466785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731468779","data":{"timestamp":" 947731468778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731471294","data":{"timestamp":" 947731471294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731477150","data":{"timestamp":" 947731477150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731479076","data":{"timestamp":" 947731479076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731481714","data":{"timestamp":" 947731481714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINACHOKUWEZESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731483568","data":{"timestamp":" 947731483567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731485906","data":{"timestamp":" 947731485906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIMBIAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731493196","data":{"timestamp":" 947731493196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAARUFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731497910","data":{"timestamp":" 947731497910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731507141","data":{"timestamp":" 947731507141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731509322","data":{"timestamp":" 947731509322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731519770","data":{"timestamp":" 947731519770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731520928","data":{"timestamp":" 947731520928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731527235","data":{"timestamp":" 947731527235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" START_MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731529083","data":{"timestamp":" 947731529083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731531629","data":{"timestamp":" 947731531629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731534003","data":{"timestamp":" 947731534003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731536769","data":{"timestamp":" 947731536769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731541876","data":{"timestamp":" 947731541876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731550925","data":{"timestamp":" 947731550925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731554908","data":{"timestamp":" 947731554908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731557831","data":{"timestamp":" 947731557831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731562277","data":{"timestamp":" 947731562277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGELIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731564904","data":{"timestamp":" 947731564904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731566799","data":{"timestamp":" 947731566799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731571493","data":{"timestamp":" 947731571493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731573954","data":{"timestamp":" 947731573954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731576036","data":{"timestamp":" 947731576036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731578149","data":{"timestamp":" 947731578148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731582977","data":{"timestamp":" 947731582976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731585593","data":{"timestamp":" 947731585593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731587985","data":{"timestamp":" 947731587985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731591843","data":{"timestamp":" 947731591843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUONYESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731593858","data":{"timestamp":" 947731593858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731595553","data":{"timestamp":" 947731595553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731597872","data":{"timestamp":" 947731597872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731600935","data":{"timestamp":" 947731600935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UKOKE"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731602941","data":{"timestamp":" 947731602941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKOKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731605260","data":{"timestamp":" 947731605260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731606781","data":{"timestamp":" 947731606781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731607139","data":{"timestamp":" 947731607139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731609117","data":{"timestamp":" 947731609117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUSANYA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731610625","data":{"timestamp":" 947731610625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUSANYA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731612493","data":{"timestamp":" 947731612493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUSANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731616116","data":{"timestamp":" 947731616116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731616874","data":{"timestamp":" 947731616874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731618879","data":{"timestamp":" 947731618878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731622022","data":{"timestamp":" 947731622022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731623966","data":{"timestamp":" 947731623966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731625834","data":{"timestamp":" 947731625834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731627992","data":{"timestamp":" 947731627991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731630083","data":{"timestamp":" 947731630083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731632257","data":{"timestamp":" 947731632257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731633972","data":{"timestamp":" 947731633972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IWEKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731636856","data":{"timestamp":" 947731636856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731638682","data":{"timestamp":" 947731638682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731643707","data":{"timestamp":" 947731643707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731645660","data":{"timestamp":" 947731645660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731647807","data":{"timestamp":" 947731647806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731651648","data":{"timestamp":" 947731651648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731654085","data":{"timestamp":" 947731654085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731657317","data":{"timestamp":" 947731657317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731659437","data":{"timestamp":" 947731659437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nateketea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731662042","data":{"timestamp":" 947731662042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nateketea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731664329","data":{"timestamp":" 947731664329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nateketea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NATEKETEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731667304","data":{"timestamp":" 947731667303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nateketea!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NATEKETEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731669430","data":{"timestamp":" 947731669430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alifurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731672801","data":{"timestamp":" 947731672800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alifurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731674890","data":{"timestamp":" 947731674890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMHIMIZA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMHIMIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731675890","data":{"timestamp":" 947731675890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMHIMIZA"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731677837","data":{"timestamp":" 947731677836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMHIMIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731680730","data":{"timestamp":" 947731680730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731683706","data":{"timestamp":" 947731683706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731687323","data":{"timestamp":" 947731687323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AENDELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731692670","data":{"timestamp":" 947731692670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731693737","data":{"timestamp":" 947731693736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731698889","data":{"timestamp":" 947731698889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731698975","data":{"timestamp":" 947731698974"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAANAKE"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731705659","data":{"timestamp":" 947731705659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAANAKE"," userResponse":" START_MAANAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731707552","data":{"timestamp":" 947731707552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731708627","data":{"timestamp":" 947731708627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731711796","data":{"timestamp":" 947731711796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731714383","data":{"timestamp":" 947731714382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" START_ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731715605","data":{"timestamp":" 947731715605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731718777","data":{"timestamp":" 947731718777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731719931","data":{"timestamp":" 947731719931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731721291","data":{"timestamp":" 947731721291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731725766","data":{"timestamp":" 947731725765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731728131","data":{"timestamp":" 947731728130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731729618","data":{"timestamp":" 947731729617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731730883","data":{"timestamp":" 947731730883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731732382","data":{"timestamp":" 947731732382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731733765","data":{"timestamp":" 947731733765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731735365","data":{"timestamp":" 947731735365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" INGELIKUWA"," userResponse":" MAANAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731739238","data":{"timestamp":" 947731739238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGELIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731744115","data":{"timestamp":" 947731744115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731748638","data":{"timestamp":" 947731748638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731750575","data":{"timestamp":" 947731750574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731752721","data":{"timestamp":" 947731752721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731752724","data":{"timestamp":" 947731752724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731752727","data":{"timestamp":" 947731752727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731756154","data":{"timestamp":" 947731756154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIJERUHIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731761651","data":{"timestamp":" 947731761651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VIBAYA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731764624","data":{"timestamp":" 947731764624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIBAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731768296","data":{"timestamp":" 947731768296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731770865","data":{"timestamp":" 947731770865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731773732","data":{"timestamp":" 947731773732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731777180","data":{"timestamp":" 947731777180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731777778","data":{"timestamp":" 947731777778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOTONI"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731781505","data":{"timestamp":" 947731781504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTONI"," userResponse":" MOTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731785236","data":{"timestamp":" 947731785235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731788449","data":{"timestamp":" 947731788449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731789214","data":{"timestamp":" 947731789214"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731792627","data":{"timestamp":" 947731792627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731792630","data":{"timestamp":" 947731792629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731798415","data":{"timestamp":" 947731798415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731802867","data":{"timestamp":" 947731802867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731804553","data":{"timestamp":" 947731804553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" HANGEWEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731806032","data":{"timestamp":" 947731806030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731809949","data":{"timestamp":" 947731809949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731813524","data":{"timestamp":" 947731813524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731815820","data":{"timestamp":" 947731815818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731820430","data":{"timestamp":" 947731820429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731822472","data":{"timestamp":" 947731822472"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731827644","data":{"timestamp":" 947731827644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731835043","data":{"timestamp":" 947731835042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731835901","data":{"timestamp":" 947731835901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731837379","data":{"timestamp":" 947731837379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731838482","data":{"timestamp":" 947731838481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEZA"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731840400","data":{"timestamp":" 947731840400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEZA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731841936","data":{"timestamp":" 947731841936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731845717","data":{"timestamp":" 947731845717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731851136","data":{"timestamp":" 947731851136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731852924","data":{"timestamp":" 947731852923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731853809","data":{"timestamp":" 947731853809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731855194","data":{"timestamp":" 947731855194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731856128","data":{"timestamp":" 947731856128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731856931","data":{"timestamp":" 947731856931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731860521","data":{"timestamp":" 947731860521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731864703","data":{"timestamp":" 947731864703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731867769","data":{"timestamp":" 947731867768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731870656","data":{"timestamp":" 947731870655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHECHEMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731873637","data":{"timestamp":" 947731873637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731879057","data":{"timestamp":" 947731879056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731882113","data":{"timestamp":" 947731882112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731884652","data":{"timestamp":" 947731884652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731888392","data":{"timestamp":" 947731888391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731893910","data":{"timestamp":" 947731893910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731896963","data":{"timestamp":" 947731896963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731896966","data":{"timestamp":" 947731896966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731899151","data":{"timestamp":" 947731899151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731902236","data":{"timestamp":" 947731902236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731904241","data":{"timestamp":" 947731904240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731907132","data":{"timestamp":" 947731907132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731909237","data":{"timestamp":" 947731909236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731911257","data":{"timestamp":" 947731911256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731911407","data":{"timestamp":" 947731911407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731977947","data":{"timestamp":" 947731977946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" f2eb5480-2898-4107-9fbb-65bdf62fae22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731993996","data":{"timestamp":" 947731993996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731996218","data":{"timestamp":" 947731996218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947731999356","data":{"timestamp":" 947731999356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732010622","data":{"timestamp":" 947732010622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732013631","data":{"timestamp":" 947732013631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732016451","data":{"timestamp":" 947732016451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732017322","data":{"timestamp":" 947732017322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732021329","data":{"timestamp":" 947732021329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIKE"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732023239","data":{"timestamp":" 947732023238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732027779","data":{"timestamp":" 947732027778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732031953","data":{"timestamp":" 947732031952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732035230","data":{"timestamp":" 947732035230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDOKANDO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732039478","data":{"timestamp":" 947732039478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732043395","data":{"timestamp":" 947732043395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732048936","data":{"timestamp":" 947732048936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIWAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732051575","data":{"timestamp":" 947732051575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732054871","data":{"timestamp":" 947732054871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732057960","data":{"timestamp":" 947732057959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAWAULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732060301","data":{"timestamp":" 947732060301"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732063637","data":{"timestamp":" 947732063637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732065514","data":{"timestamp":" 947732065514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732068290","data":{"timestamp":" 947732068290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732070792","data":{"timestamp":" 947732070792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732072603","data":{"timestamp":" 947732072603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732075046","data":{"timestamp":" 947732075046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732082132","data":{"timestamp":" 947732082131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732094129","data":{"timestamp":" 947732094129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732096922","data":{"timestamp":" 947732096922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732098739","data":{"timestamp":" 947732098739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732104554","data":{"timestamp":" 947732104554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732107627","data":{"timestamp":" 947732107626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732109708","data":{"timestamp":" 947732109707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732112145","data":{"timestamp":" 947732112145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732117695","data":{"timestamp":" 947732117695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732119960","data":{"timestamp":" 947732119960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732123927","data":{"timestamp":" 947732123926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732128658","data":{"timestamp":" 947732128658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732132816","data":{"timestamp":" 947732132816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732136289","data":{"timestamp":" 947732136289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732143344","data":{"timestamp":" 947732143343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732147055","data":{"timestamp":" 947732147055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732148896","data":{"timestamp":" 947732148896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732152061","data":{"timestamp":" 947732152061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732154891","data":{"timestamp":" 947732154890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732158142","data":{"timestamp":" 947732158142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732163057","data":{"timestamp":" 947732163056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732166635","data":{"timestamp":" 947732166634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732170926","data":{"timestamp":" 947732170926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732177430","data":{"timestamp":" 947732177430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732179762","data":{"timestamp":" 947732179762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732183323","data":{"timestamp":" 947732183323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732192685","data":{"timestamp":" 947732192685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732194952","data":{"timestamp":" 947732194952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732199753","data":{"timestamp":" 947732199753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732201798","data":{"timestamp":" 947732201797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732205775","data":{"timestamp":" 947732205774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" START_KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732208266","data":{"timestamp":" 947732208265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732217628","data":{"timestamp":" 947732217628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732226978","data":{"timestamp":" 947732226978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732232432","data":{"timestamp":" 947732232432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALISAIDIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732243229","data":{"timestamp":" 947732243229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732254018","data":{"timestamp":" 947732254018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732257632","data":{"timestamp":" 947732257632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732260852","data":{"timestamp":" 947732260852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732263110","data":{"timestamp":" 947732263110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732264380","data":{"timestamp":" 947732264380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732266419","data":{"timestamp":" 947732266419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732266422","data":{"timestamp":" 947732266422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732269392","data":{"timestamp":" 947732269391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732274540","data":{"timestamp":" 947732274540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732275811","data":{"timestamp":" 947732275811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732279895","data":{"timestamp":" 947732279895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIFUATA"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732284547","data":{"timestamp":" 947732284547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIFUATA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732286399","data":{"timestamp":" 947732286399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732287073","data":{"timestamp":" 947732287072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732288876","data":{"timestamp":" 947732288876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732290843","data":{"timestamp":" 947732290843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732291402","data":{"timestamp":" 947732291402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732291862","data":{"timestamp":" 947732291861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" START_MSICHANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732299696","data":{"timestamp":" 947732299695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732301262","data":{"timestamp":" 947732301262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732301530","data":{"timestamp":" 947732301530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732306079","data":{"timestamp":" 947732306079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732308229","data":{"timestamp":" 947732308228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732316532","data":{"timestamp":" 947732316532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732319560","data":{"timestamp":" 947732319560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732323453","data":{"timestamp":" 947732323453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732326767","data":{"timestamp":" 947732326767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732331556","data":{"timestamp":" 947732331556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732337315","data":{"timestamp":" 947732337315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732339133","data":{"timestamp":" 947732339133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732342920","data":{"timestamp":" 947732342919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732343982","data":{"timestamp":" 947732343982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732345888","data":{"timestamp":" 947732345888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732349413","data":{"timestamp":" 947732349413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732356898","data":{"timestamp":" 947732356898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732359366","data":{"timestamp":" 947732359366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732359982","data":{"timestamp":" 947732359981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732360101","data":{"timestamp":" 947732360101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 8cc7a4dd-d736-494e-922f-1139c0e9d2a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732370751","data":{"timestamp":" 947732370751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 6da761bf-aab0-46cc-96e2-58377a6bc19d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732370981","data":{"timestamp":" 947732370981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 6da761bf-aab0-46cc-96e2-58377a6bc19d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732371956","data":{"timestamp":" 947732371955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 6da761bf-aab0-46cc-96e2-58377a6bc19d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732373243","data":{"timestamp":" 947732373242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 6da761bf-aab0-46cc-96e2-58377a6bc19d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732375368","data":{"timestamp":" 947732375367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 6da761bf-aab0-46cc-96e2-58377a6bc19d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732388074","data":{"timestamp":" 947732388073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732388308","data":{"timestamp":" 947732388308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732389280","data":{"timestamp":" 947732389280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732390560","data":{"timestamp":" 947732390560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732393531","data":{"timestamp":" 947732393531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732394393","data":{"timestamp":" 947732394392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732394720","data":{"timestamp":" 947732394720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732395969","data":{"timestamp":" 947732395968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732399525","data":{"timestamp":" 947732399523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732400518","data":{"timestamp":" 947732400517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732400781","data":{"timestamp":" 947732400779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732401741","data":{"timestamp":" 947732401740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732404636","data":{"timestamp":" 947732404636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732405682","data":{"timestamp":" 947732405681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732406163","data":{"timestamp":" 947732406163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732410741","data":{"timestamp":" 947732410739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732410862","data":{"timestamp":" 947732410862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 96b5045f-9298-4764-9ea1-b035417ee01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732425475","data":{"timestamp":" 947732425475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732427712","data":{"timestamp":" 947732427712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZALIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732430036","data":{"timestamp":" 947732430036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732432471","data":{"timestamp":" 947732432471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732437566","data":{"timestamp":" 947732437566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732441074","data":{"timestamp":" 947732441074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732444726","data":{"timestamp":" 947732444726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732448589","data":{"timestamp":" 947732448589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" UHURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732450267","data":{"timestamp":" 947732450266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732450277","data":{"timestamp":" 947732450276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732454131","data":{"timestamp":" 947732454131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732464430","data":{"timestamp":" 947732464430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732465295","data":{"timestamp":" 947732465294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" START_WAMEPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732466988","data":{"timestamp":" 947732466987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732469164","data":{"timestamp":" 947732469164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" WAMEPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732471782","data":{"timestamp":" 947732471782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732474185","data":{"timestamp":" 947732474185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732477169","data":{"timestamp":" 947732477169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732479716","data":{"timestamp":" 947732479716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732484799","data":{"timestamp":" 947732484799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732485711","data":{"timestamp":" 947732485711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" HAWAKUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732487831","data":{"timestamp":" 947732487831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732488912","data":{"timestamp":" 947732488912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732491802","data":{"timestamp":" 947732491801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732494251","data":{"timestamp":" 947732494251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732495849","data":{"timestamp":" 947732495848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732500248","data":{"timestamp":" 947732500247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732501331","data":{"timestamp":" 947732501331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732502722","data":{"timestamp":" 947732502722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732504708","data":{"timestamp":" 947732504708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732505127","data":{"timestamp":" 947732505127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732506710","data":{"timestamp":" 947732506710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732511010","data":{"timestamp":" 947732511010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732511961","data":{"timestamp":" 947732511961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732517230","data":{"timestamp":" 947732517229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732518836","data":{"timestamp":" 947732518836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732519989","data":{"timestamp":" 947732519989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732522029","data":{"timestamp":" 947732522029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732522032","data":{"timestamp":" 947732522032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732525608","data":{"timestamp":" 947732525608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" WAMEPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732526790","data":{"timestamp":" 947732526790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732527893","data":{"timestamp":" 947732527893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" START_NDOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732529995","data":{"timestamp":" 947732529995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732531413","data":{"timestamp":" 947732531412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732535410","data":{"timestamp":" 947732535410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732536963","data":{"timestamp":" 947732536962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732539525","data":{"timestamp":" 947732539525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," userResponse":" START_HAINGEWEZEKANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732540710","data":{"timestamp":" 947732540710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," userResponse":" START_KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732542865","data":{"timestamp":" 947732542864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732544491","data":{"timestamp":" 947732544490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" START_MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732545595","data":{"timestamp":" 947732545595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732549274","data":{"timestamp":" 947732549274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732551012","data":{"timestamp":" 947732551012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ANGEKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732551854","data":{"timestamp":" 947732551854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732553479","data":{"timestamp":" 947732553478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732555532","data":{"timestamp":" 947732555532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MZALIWA"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732557081","data":{"timestamp":" 947732557081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MZALIWA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732559027","data":{"timestamp":" 947732559026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZALIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732559311","data":{"timestamp":" 947732559311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732562224","data":{"timestamp":" 947732562224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732562533","data":{"timestamp":" 947732562532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732564866","data":{"timestamp":" 947732564865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LICHA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732566399","data":{"timestamp":" 947732566399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LICHA"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732567904","data":{"timestamp":" 947732567903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LICHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732568395","data":{"timestamp":" 947732568395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732570696","data":{"timestamp":" 947732570696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" ANGEKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732571989","data":{"timestamp":" 947732571988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732574357","data":{"timestamp":" 947732574357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732577581","data":{"timestamp":" 947732577581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732577769","data":{"timestamp":" 947732577769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732579478","data":{"timestamp":" 947732579478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732580829","data":{"timestamp":" 947732580829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732582841","data":{"timestamp":" 947732582841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732586841","data":{"timestamp":" 947732586841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732592810","data":{"timestamp":" 947732592810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732595874","data":{"timestamp":" 947732595874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732598314","data":{"timestamp":" 947732598313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732600583","data":{"timestamp":" 947732600583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732602335","data":{"timestamp":" 947732602335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732604863","data":{"timestamp":" 947732604863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732608070","data":{"timestamp":" 947732608070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732610956","data":{"timestamp":" 947732610956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732613705","data":{"timestamp":" 947732613705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732615720","data":{"timestamp":" 947732615719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732619715","data":{"timestamp":" 947732619715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732621720","data":{"timestamp":" 947732621719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732628206","data":{"timestamp":" 947732628206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEENDA"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732631018","data":{"timestamp":" 947732631018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEENDA"," userResponse":" ANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732632766","data":{"timestamp":" 947732632766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732633926","data":{"timestamp":" 947732633926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732634304","data":{"timestamp":" 947732634304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732636032","data":{"timestamp":" 947732636032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732637295","data":{"timestamp":" 947732637295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ANGEENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732639051","data":{"timestamp":" 947732639051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732642539","data":{"timestamp":" 947732642539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732644199","data":{"timestamp":" 947732644198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732646616","data":{"timestamp":" 947732646616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGEMSAIDIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732648944","data":{"timestamp":" 947732648944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732654194","data":{"timestamp":" 947732654194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732656146","data":{"timestamp":" 947732656146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732658859","data":{"timestamp":" 947732658859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732660937","data":{"timestamp":" 947732660937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTIMIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732662890","data":{"timestamp":" 947732662890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732664589","data":{"timestamp":" 947732664589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732667076","data":{"timestamp":" 947732667076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732669225","data":{"timestamp":" 947732669224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732671009","data":{"timestamp":" 947732671009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732672657","data":{"timestamp":" 947732672657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732674460","data":{"timestamp":" 947732674460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732676741","data":{"timestamp":" 947732676741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732679082","data":{"timestamp":" 947732679082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732681572","data":{"timestamp":" 947732681572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732683805","data":{"timestamp":" 947732683805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPEWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732685794","data":{"timestamp":" 947732685794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732687994","data":{"timestamp":" 947732687994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUAMBATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732692614","data":{"timestamp":" 947732692614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732695120","data":{"timestamp":" 947732695120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UREMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732696681","data":{"timestamp":" 947732696681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732699509","data":{"timestamp":" 947732699509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732701411","data":{"timestamp":" 947732701411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732703582","data":{"timestamp":" 947732703582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KADRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732706575","data":{"timestamp":" 947732706574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732709003","data":{"timestamp":" 947732709003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732712456","data":{"timestamp":" 947732712455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYOYOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732714146","data":{"timestamp":" 947732714145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732715989","data":{"timestamp":" 947732715989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732718935","data":{"timestamp":" 947732718935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732721199","data":{"timestamp":" 947732721198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULETA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732723337","data":{"timestamp":" 947732723337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732725084","data":{"timestamp":" 947732725084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732727566","data":{"timestamp":" 947732727566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732730832","data":{"timestamp":" 947732730832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732733328","data":{"timestamp":" 947732733328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732735679","data":{"timestamp":" 947732735679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732739133","data":{"timestamp":" 947732739133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732741454","data":{"timestamp":" 947732741454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732744060","data":{"timestamp":" 947732744059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732746330","data":{"timestamp":" 947732746330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732748240","data":{"timestamp":" 947732748240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732751871","data":{"timestamp":" 947732751871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732755450","data":{"timestamp":" 947732755450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732757541","data":{"timestamp":" 947732757541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732759821","data":{"timestamp":" 947732759821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732761651","data":{"timestamp":" 947732761651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBALO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732763882","data":{"timestamp":" 947732763882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEBADILISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732766053","data":{"timestamp":" 947732766053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732767701","data":{"timestamp":" 947732767701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732769753","data":{"timestamp":" 947732769753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732773003","data":{"timestamp":" 947732773003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHISANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732775052","data":{"timestamp":" 947732775052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUSOMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732777074","data":{"timestamp":" 947732777074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732778482","data":{"timestamp":" 947732778482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732781238","data":{"timestamp":" 947732781238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732783732","data":{"timestamp":" 947732783731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732785320","data":{"timestamp":" 947732785319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732788413","data":{"timestamp":" 947732788413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732790252","data":{"timestamp":" 947732790252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732792462","data":{"timestamp":" 947732792462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732794411","data":{"timestamp":" 947732794411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732798600","data":{"timestamp":" 947732798599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732801596","data":{"timestamp":" 947732801596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732803591","data":{"timestamp":" 947732803591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732807251","data":{"timestamp":" 947732807251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732809936","data":{"timestamp":" 947732809936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJUE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732812288","data":{"timestamp":" 947732812288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732814162","data":{"timestamp":" 947732814162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732817714","data":{"timestamp":" 947732817714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732820317","data":{"timestamp":" 947732820317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732822523","data":{"timestamp":" 947732822522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732825751","data":{"timestamp":" 947732825751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732827752","data":{"timestamp":" 947732827751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732833027","data":{"timestamp":" 947732833026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732834834","data":{"timestamp":" 947732834834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732837331","data":{"timestamp":" 947732837331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732840086","data":{"timestamp":" 947732840086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732842246","data":{"timestamp":" 947732842246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732844458","data":{"timestamp":" 947732844458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732846272","data":{"timestamp":" 947732846271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732848337","data":{"timestamp":" 947732848336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732850787","data":{"timestamp":" 947732850787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732853516","data":{"timestamp":" 947732853516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732855523","data":{"timestamp":" 947732855523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732860069","data":{"timestamp":" 947732860069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732864166","data":{"timestamp":" 947732864165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732868197","data":{"timestamp":" 947732868197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732870124","data":{"timestamp":" 947732870124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732873513","data":{"timestamp":" 947732873513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732875691","data":{"timestamp":" 947732875691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732877685","data":{"timestamp":" 947732877685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732880395","data":{"timestamp":" 947732880394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732883462","data":{"timestamp":" 947732883462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PORTUGAL"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732885630","data":{"timestamp":" 947732885630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732888313","data":{"timestamp":" 947732888313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732893133","data":{"timestamp":" 947732893133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732895511","data":{"timestamp":" 947732895511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732897988","data":{"timestamp":" 947732897988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LUGHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732900315","data":{"timestamp":" 947732900315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732905654","data":{"timestamp":" 947732905654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732908171","data":{"timestamp":" 947732908171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732922862","data":{"timestamp":" 947732922862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732925453","data":{"timestamp":" 947732925453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732928746","data":{"timestamp":" 947732928746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732931858","data":{"timestamp":" 947732931858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732934181","data":{"timestamp":" 947732934181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732936118","data":{"timestamp":" 947732936118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732938260","data":{"timestamp":" 947732938260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732940690","data":{"timestamp":" 947732940690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732943096","data":{"timestamp":" 947732943096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732945557","data":{"timestamp":" 947732945557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732951825","data":{"timestamp":" 947732951824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" IKITIMIA"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732953931","data":{"timestamp":" 947732953931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITIMIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732956224","data":{"timestamp":" 947732956224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732958689","data":{"timestamp":" 947732958689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732960529","data":{"timestamp":" 947732960529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732962256","data":{"timestamp":" 947732962256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732964077","data":{"timestamp":" 947732964077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732966433","data":{"timestamp":" 947732966433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732969164","data":{"timestamp":" 947732969163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732970953","data":{"timestamp":" 947732970953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732976291","data":{"timestamp":" 947732976291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732978768","data":{"timestamp":" 947732978767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732980501","data":{"timestamp":" 947732980501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732982730","data":{"timestamp":" 947732982730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732984604","data":{"timestamp":" 947732984604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732989601","data":{"timestamp":" 947732989601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732992139","data":{"timestamp":" 947732992139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732994350","data":{"timestamp":" 947732994350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732996561","data":{"timestamp":" 947732996560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947732997942","data":{"timestamp":" 947732997941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733000311","data":{"timestamp":" 947733000311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733002473","data":{"timestamp":" 947733002473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733004433","data":{"timestamp":" 947733004433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733008775","data":{"timestamp":" 947733008775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733011289","data":{"timestamp":" 947733011289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733014358","data":{"timestamp":" 947733014358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733017325","data":{"timestamp":" 947733017325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733019139","data":{"timestamp":" 947733019139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733021937","data":{"timestamp":" 947733021937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUMAINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733023846","data":{"timestamp":" 947733023846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733025777","data":{"timestamp":" 947733025777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733028098","data":{"timestamp":" 947733028098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733030497","data":{"timestamp":" 947733030497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733033389","data":{"timestamp":" 947733033389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733035306","data":{"timestamp":" 947733035305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733040991","data":{"timestamp":" 947733040991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733043350","data":{"timestamp":" 947733043350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733048224","data":{"timestamp":" 947733048224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733050133","data":{"timestamp":" 947733050133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733052442","data":{"timestamp":" 947733052441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733054311","data":{"timestamp":" 947733054311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733055865","data":{"timestamp":" 947733055865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733057799","data":{"timestamp":" 947733057799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733059940","data":{"timestamp":" 947733059940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733065308","data":{"timestamp":" 947733065308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733067594","data":{"timestamp":" 947733067594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733071667","data":{"timestamp":" 947733071666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733075768","data":{"timestamp":" 947733075768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733078549","data":{"timestamp":" 947733078548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733080920","data":{"timestamp":" 947733080920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733083028","data":{"timestamp":" 947733083028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733085489","data":{"timestamp":" 947733085488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733087159","data":{"timestamp":" 947733087159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733089018","data":{"timestamp":" 947733089018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULETA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733091426","data":{"timestamp":" 947733091426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABADILIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733093904","data":{"timestamp":" 947733093903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733096097","data":{"timestamp":" 947733096097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733096929","data":{"timestamp":" 947733096929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAIS"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733097988","data":{"timestamp":" 947733097988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYECHAGULIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733100858","data":{"timestamp":" 947733100858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUIONGOZA"," userResponse":" MACGEL"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733104174","data":{"timestamp":" 947733104173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUIONGOZA"," userResponse":" START_KUIONGOZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733106125","data":{"timestamp":" 947733106124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIONGOZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733106311","data":{"timestamp":" 947733106311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHI"," userResponse":" NCHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733106319","data":{"timestamp":" 947733106319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733108501","data":{"timestamp":" 947733108501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733112830","data":{"timestamp":" 947733112829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733115441","data":{"timestamp":" 947733115441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733117471","data":{"timestamp":" 947733117471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733117632","data":{"timestamp":" 947733117632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAMORA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733120367","data":{"timestamp":" 947733120367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMORA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733122603","data":{"timestamp":" 947733122603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACGEL"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733125055","data":{"timestamp":" 947733125055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPENDANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733126778","data":{"timestamp":" 947733126777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733130242","data":{"timestamp":" 947733130242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733133682","data":{"timestamp":" 947733133682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733135737","data":{"timestamp":" 947733135736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPEWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733137647","data":{"timestamp":" 947733137647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733140134","data":{"timestamp":" 947733140134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKUHAKIKISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733142149","data":{"timestamp":" 947733142149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733144287","data":{"timestamp":" 947733144287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733146431","data":{"timestamp":" 947733146431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733148792","data":{"timestamp":" 947733148792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733150880","data":{"timestamp":" 947733150880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733153548","data":{"timestamp":" 947733153548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733154306","data":{"timestamp":" 947733154306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733155708","data":{"timestamp":" 947733155708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733157256","data":{"timestamp":" 947733157256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733158911","data":{"timestamp":" 947733158911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMU"," userResponse":" START_WALIPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733162747","data":{"timestamp":" 947733162747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733164661","data":{"timestamp":" 947733164661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733168574","data":{"timestamp":" 947733168574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733172946","data":{"timestamp":" 947733172946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733174706","data":{"timestamp":" 947733174706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733177493","data":{"timestamp":" 947733177493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733179472","data":{"timestamp":" 947733179471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733179564","data":{"timestamp":" 947733179564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 57b29920-957e-48cb-b096-1a4c0272c9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733187702","data":{"timestamp":" 947733187702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 3d9e644e-61bd-4193-a77a-d42a40ab2cf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733192462","data":{"timestamp":" 947733192462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 3d9e644e-61bd-4193-a77a-d42a40ab2cf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733198040","data":{"timestamp":" 947733198040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 3d9e644e-61bd-4193-a77a-d42a40ab2cf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733204737","data":{"timestamp":" 947733204737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 3d9e644e-61bd-4193-a77a-d42a40ab2cf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733210149","data":{"timestamp":" 947733210148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 3d9e644e-61bd-4193-a77a-d42a40ab2cf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733220513","data":{"timestamp":" 947733220513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_053710"," gameId":" 3d9e644e-61bd-4193-a77a-d42a40ab2cf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}